CURRICULIM VITAE

PERSONAL DETAILS

NAME: NYAOKE BRIAN ANTONY

DATE OF BIRTH: 1st MAY 1995

GENDER: MALE

MARITAL STATUS: SINGLE

ID NUMBER: 32681856

CITIZENSHIP: KENYAN

RELIGION: CHRISTIAN

LANGUAGE: HIGH PROFICIENCY IN WRITTEN AND SPOKEN ENGLISH AND KISWAHILI

TELEPHONE NUMBER: +254 707495465

EMAIL: briyoantony@gmail.com

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

I am an undergraduate student from Meru university of Science and Technology with a bachelors degree's in **Computer** Technology attaining a second class honours (upper division). I have a wealth of experience in computer services and operations at the ground level. I am self-driven, hardworking, a good team builder and with excellent communication skills. I have shown sound, good leadership skills at the community and the entire society.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To play a key role in optimizing access to technology in Africa and using my skills in IT to make applications that solves our daily problems.

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

- September, 2019: Scientific Computing and Python for Data Science at WorldQuant University
- 2. January, 2016: Networking- CISCO at Kenya Methodist University (KEMU)
- 3. 2014-2018: Undergraduate program at Meru University.

- 4. 2010-2013: High school Student at Nyabondo Boys High School
- 5. 2001-2009: Primary School pupil at Muhoroni Furaha Academy

WORK EXPERIENCE

- October 2020- Present: ICT Intern Milimani Law Courts under the Presidential Digital Talent Program.
- November 2018 February 2019: Intern Samasourse Digital Basics Nairobi working as an IT technician and a Data Entry Office for the human machine interaction program.
- May 16th, 2016-AUGUST 2016: IT user support and system maintenance at Kenya Revenue Authority Southern Region Mombasa.
- May 15th 2015-September 2015: Computer Technician At BestBuy's Baroda Brunch in Mombasa.
- ➤ January 8th 2014-12th August 2014: Records management at Nyabondo Mission Hospital(Developed a database system to automate their record keeping process)

INTERESTS

- Learning and practicing data science and artificial intelligence.
- Developing real life solving applications.
- Getting involved in community work and projects.
- Food production in my own farm and value addition.

HOBBIES

- Networking
- Programming
- Playing Rugby

REFEREES

1. MARY WALOWE

MERU UNIVERSITY OF SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY

COURSE ADVISOR

TEL NO: +254 724 789102

2. CECILIA MWAMINO

KENYA REVENUE AUTHORITY

TEL NO: +254 721 712773

3. ALBERT ATAMBO

ICT Manager Kenya Revenue Authority

P.O.BOX 48240 Nairobi.

TEL NO: 0717077590